(Amy:)I know how you feel.
(Amy:)Sheldon ignored me for a week
when he got that Roomba vacuum.
(Amy:)I kick it when he's not looking.
(Bernadette:)What are they doing?
(Howard:)They're drinking beer
and watching football.
(Bernadette:)So why don't you do that
with them?
(Howard:)-They don't want me.
-What do you mean?
(Howard:)Well, Sheldon started talking
about how his dad isn't alive anymore,
(Howard:)and they were toasting,
and I tried to tell them
(Howard:)about how sad I was
when my dad abandoned--
(Amy:)Zack's here!
(Raj:)Stir the gravy.
(Bernadette:)Sorry. I really want
to hear how sad you are.
(Bernadette:)I'll be back in, like, five, ten minutes.
Sony she made you come
over here on a holiday.
(Zack:)It's all right.
I didn't have anything going on.
(Zack:)Plus, Penny told me we're married,
(Zack:)and Thanksgiving's a time
to be with family.
(Penny:)Yeah, okay great.
(Penny:)Can we just get this over with?
Yeah, you guys
have to sign here and here.
(Leonard:)On Monday,
we'll tile for the annulment,